漫威影业出品
十年前
原创翻译  双语字幕
■
仅供学习 禁止用于任何商业盈利行为
更多影视更新
请登陆www.ZiMuZu.tv
■
翻译：夜魔开  腋毛暴徒
翻译：夜魔章鱼  Silence
校对：夜魔奶
味道跟鱼卵一样
Oh, it tastes like fish eggs.
时间轴：夜魔念  夜魔萌
我觉得这就是鱼卵  爱因斯坦
I think they are, Einstein.
而且价格高达一盎司两百美元
And it tops out at $200 an ounce.
后期：聪炒吉丁  8T     总监：夜魔奶
你们俩真觉得自个儿能硬闯这个聚会吗
You two really think you can crash this party?
-是的  -我们很有野心
- Yes. - We're kind of ambitious.
打开微信   扫描左侧二维码
或搜索公众号:    美剧炸了
了解最新影视资讯字幕信息
-你要把我们踢出去吗哥们  -看情况
- Are you gonna kick us out, bro? - Depends.
你们是自大的蠢蛋吗
Are you pompous jackasses?
我们  并不自大
Uh, well, we're not... pompous.
自便吧
Help yourself.
对这味道还上瘾了
Mmm, the taste kind of grows on you.
你要坐下来尝尝吗  搬个凳子过来
You wanna get down on this? Pull up a stool.
你吃吧  我去拿点酒
Uh, you do that. I'm gonna find the alcohol.
真聪明  给我也拿瓶啤酒
Genius! And grab me a beer!
那不是可住宿的游艇  就是艘快艇
It's not a cabin cruiser, it's a yacht.
我们付给道尔顿的那两万四千美元
For the $24,000 we're paying Dalton,
最好杰克逊的现代舞能包含在内
I would expect Jackson's modern dance to be included.
我喜欢今年喷气机队的比赛
I like the way the Jets are playing this year.
-借过  -该走了
- Excuse me. - It's time to go.
-不  我还要找  -你找到了
- No, I'm just looking for-- - You found it.
走吧
Come on.
他跟我一起的
He's with me.
抱歉
Excuse me.
夜
魔
侠
第二季  第五集
德啤  喝起来跟尿一样
Mmm! German beer. Tastes like piss.
你在这儿干什么
What the hell are you doing here?
想找你还不简单
You've never been hard to find.
我问的不是那个
That's not what I asked.
起码你的家具换了更好的
At least your furniture's improved.
有点怀念我的旧蒲团了
Kinda liked my old futon.
我很喜欢用的
I liked breaking it in.
地方不错
Nice place.
但衣服品味太差了
Too bad about the clothes, though.
你为什么在这儿
Why are you here?
如果我说想你了你信吗
Would you believe it if I said I missed you?
-不信  -聪明
- No. - Smart man.
哥伦比亚大学的教育还算有点用
Columbia education really paid off.
跟你没啥关系
No thanks to you.
我来纽约开个会  想着过来看看
I'm in New York for a meeting. I thought I'd pop by.
你不能在这儿过夜  所以
Well, you're not staying here, so...
好吧
Fine.
那就去我在市中心的顶层公寓吧
My penthouse in midtown will just have to do, then.
我们在那儿共度了几个春宵
We spent some nights there.
听着  如果你来是为了回忆往事的话
Look, if you came here to walk down memory lane,
-我真的没有那个  -对不起
- I don't really have the-- - I'm sorry.
我用了很多年想说服自己
I've spent years trying to convince myself
万事皆有因
that things happen for a reason,
我和你并非天生一对
that you and I were not meant to be.
但我现在知道了  那不是命中注定
But I know now. That wasn't fate.
那只是选择
It was a choice.
我的选择
My choice.
我很抱歉
And I'm sorry.
我在这世上没别人了  马修
I'm alone in the world, Matthew.
你知道那什么感觉吗
Do you know what that feels like?
你当然知道
Of course you do.
你也知道收拾你父亲烂摊子是什么感觉
And you know what it's like to clean up your father's messes.
很久以前  他还没死的时候
A long time ago, before he died,
我父亲和罗克森公司有业务来往
my father did business with the Roxxon Corporation.
罗克森
Roxxon?
能源  清洁用品  通心粉和芝士
Energy, cleaning supplies, macaroni and cheese.
使用童工  贩卖奴隶
Child labor, slave trade.
他们在各领域都有涉足
They have their fingers in everything.
我相信这叫分散投资
I believe it's called diversification.
多亏我父亲糟糕的投资
And thanks to my father's shitty investments,
他们拿到了他大部分的财产
they hold most of his wealth.
好吧  我
Yeah, okay, I...
我明天跟他们董事会
I have a meeting tomorrow with the board
在夜迦富大楼开会
at the Yakatomi Building.
我需要你的帮助  马修
And I need your help, Matthew.
我能怎么帮你
How am I supposed to help you?
我希望你能用你花大钱学来的法律知识
I want you to use that expensive legal training of yours
帮我把钱拿回来
to help me get my money back.
我是个辩护律师
See, I'm a defense lawyer.
我会付你很多钱的
I'll pay you well.
我不要你的钱
I'm not taking your money.
而且就算我接了  时间也不够
And, even if I accepted, there's not enough time.
-要时间干什么  -调查研究
- For what? - Oh, just research.
账目  股东们  层级关系
Accounts, shareholders, hierarchy of the--
你有15个小时
You have 15 hours.
15小时  艾丽卡  你疯了吗
Fifteen hours, Elektra, are you insane?
马修
Matthew.
你是我唯一能信任的人
You're the only person I can trust.
亲爱的  你可不能闯进我家里
Well, sweetheart, you don't break into my house
再跟我说信任
and then talk to me about trust.
别顾虑太多
Don't overthink it.
就是一帮商界人士
It's just a bunch of guys in business suits.
他们还没反应过来  你就已经得手了
They won't know what hit them.
很好玩的  像以前一样
Would be fun, like old times.
我和你对好玩的理解差太远了
Oh, you and I, we have very different ideas of fun.
你怎么说都行
You can say whatever you want.
-但我了解你  -不  你不了解
- But I know you-- - No, you don't.
你不再了解了
You don't, not anymore.
永远都不会了
Not... ever again.
好吧
Well...
那挺让人失望的
that's disappointing.
滚出去
Get out.
惩罚者受到惩罚
早
Morning.
我们有什么早餐可以吃吗
We, uh, have anything for breakfast?
你是饿了还是昨晚喝多了
You hungry or hungover?
都是
Both.
好吧  你需要点钾
All right, you need some potassium,
一点电解质  还有很多咖啡因
some electrolytes, and a jolt of caffeine.
我给你
I'll give you, uh...
最后一块蒂尼齐奥夫人脆皮蜜桃馅饼
The last piece of Mrs. DiNizio's peach cobbler,
这也是办公室里最后一块吃的了
which is the last piece of anything in this office.
上周之后财政状况也没有好转
I guess our finances haven't improved since last week.
是啊  委托人可不喜欢看到门上挂着"停业"牌
Yeah, well, clients don't respond well to a "Closed" Sign.
是我的错  抱歉  福吉
Yeah, it's my fault. I'm sorry, Foggy.
不怪你
Don't be.
惩罚者被带走了
Punisher off the street.
我希望雷耶斯能高抬贵足
I'm hoping Reyes will get her jackboot off our neck
这个办公室就能恢复常态了
and this office can go back to normal.
是吗  正常  什么是正常
Oh, yeah? Normal? What's that?
马特  早上好
Matt. Uh, good morning.
嗨  凯伦
Hey, Karen.
睡得好吗
Did you sleep well?
不太好  你呢
Uh, not so much. You?
我  还不错
Me? Yeah, sure.
我是说...
I mean...
我闻到你手里拿的是咖啡
Is that coffee I can smell?
-什么  -咖啡
- Hmm? - Coffee.
没错...
Uh, yeah, um...
没错  给你们买的阿拉比卡咖啡
Yeah, arabica for all.
-每人一杯  -谢谢  你太好了
- For everyone. - Wow, thank you. You're a goddess.
好了  你俩别寒暄了  说正事
Okay, you two. Let's talk business.
潜在的客户  真正的客户  有银行存款的那种
Potential clients. Real ones. With bank in the bank.
实际上  咱们能...先说说这个吗
Uh, actually, yeah, can we, uh... talk about these first?
媒体依旧把卡塞尔描述成
The, uh, press is still painting Castle
一个神经错乱的疯子
like he's nothing more than some deranged lunatic.
他又不会为红十字会募捐
Well, it's not like our boy was out collecting for the Red Cross.
我明白  我明白  但...
I know. I know, but--
你觉得这背后有隐情
You think there's more to the story.
没错  五家报社
Exactly. I mean, five different papers
哪家都没提到他脑部中弹
and not a word about the bullet he took to the brain,
以及他的服役背景和家庭状况
or his military record, or his family.
家庭状况
Uh, his family?
是这样的...
Okay, uh...
我找到了这张照片
I found this photograph.
他和妻儿在旋转木马前拍的
It's of him and his wife and kids at the carousel.
你在哪找到这照片的
You found it where?
我闯进他家去了
I sort of broke into his house.
-你闯进哪了  -你说什么
- You did what? - What?
-我知道这不太明智  -而且还很危险
- It was ill-advised, I know. - Not to mention dangerous.
-还是违法的  -没错...
- And illegal. - Yeah--
你们说的都对
It's all that. All of that.
别给我讲道理
And I don't need a lecture
不然就把咖啡还给我
or I will take those coffees back, okay?
谢谢配合
Thank you.
不光是媒体
Look, it's not just about the press.
地检官办公室也发布了声明
The DA's office released their statement
声明漏洞百出
and it's full of holes, too.
这事不是那么简单
Something big is going on here, guys,
并且全都指向弗兰克·卡塞尔
and it all circles back to Frank Castle.
-不行  不能这样  -福吉...
- Oh, no, no, no-- - Foggy--
不行  我们已经成功躲开了射来的子弹
No, come on, we successfully dodged a metaphorical bullet
和一些舆论压力
and quite a few literal ones.
我们不该这么疯狂了
We need to be done with the crazy, guys.
我们要变得正常点
We need normal.
对不起
I'm sorry.
我很抱歉  我陷得太深了
I'm really sorry if I-- -I pushed it too far.
没关系  我...
It's okay. I just...
我觉得你对卡塞尔的判断没错  但...
Uh, I don't think you're wrong about Castle, but...
道理很简单  凯伦
it's really simple, Karen.
我...不希望你受到伤害
Just... I don't want you to get hurt.
那...
So, uh...
昨晚
Last night.
Last night?
我不明白...昨晚发生了什么
I don't-- what happened last night?
-在乔茜酒吧还是和福吉  -你啊...
- At Josie's? With Foggy? - You--
-发生了什么吗  -是啊
- Did something happen? - Yeah.
-还有我不知道的事...  -是啊
- Anything else? I don't-- - Yeah?
好吧  昨晚很美好
Yeah, it was great.
但我觉得还能做得更好
And I like to think I can do better,
如果晚餐之约没变的话
if we're still on for dinner.
没变
Uh, yeah.
说定了
It's a date.
我去
Holy shit!
-银行发来的信息  -天啊
- That was the bank. - Oh, no.
不  没什么事  是收到了一笔款
No, it's... all good. There was a deposit.
巨款
A big one.
什么...
What? Uh...
没错...
Um, yeah...
拜托  这笔钱一分钱都别动
Yeah, uh, do me a favor, don't spend any of it.
-为什么  -天啊...
- Why not? - God...
我昨晚偶遇了一个潜在客户  所以...
I was hit up by a potential client yesterday, so, I just--
是赃款吗  又是那种事
Is it dirty money? Are we doing that again?
不是  完全不是  是...
No! No, it's nothing like that. It's just, um...
我不确定能不能办成  我...
I'm not sure it's gonna work out, let me...
我先去了解一下情况  回头再跟你们说
Let me get into it, I'll-- I'll get back to you.
你好  来杯纯麦卡伦
Hey, I'm gonna have a Macallan, neat,
给这位女士来杯...
and the lady will have, uh...
再来杯伏特加马提尼
another vodka martini.
-嗅觉不错啊  -谢谢夸奖  我闻了闻
- Perceptive. - Thank you, I try.
但我可以自己点酒
But I can order my own drinks.
龙舌兰  梅斯卡尔的  你们这有的话
Tequila. Mezcal, if you have it.
多谢帮助
So, thanks for your help.
这年头可靠的安保系统不好找
It's hard to find reliable security these days.
皮鞋不错
Nice shoes.
什么
What?
翼尖皮鞋  品味不错  自己擦的吗
Wingtips. Good call. Shine them yourself?
你怎么知道的
How'd you know?
你其实很好猜
You're not exactly a tough read.
我...
I...
没准不像你想的那样
could surprise you.
不太可能
Doubt it.
好吧
All right.
那你想试试吗
You, uh, wanna give it a try?
好啊
Okay.
你很急切地寻找归属感...
You desperately want to belong somewhere...
或寻找某人
with someone,
这才是你
which is the real reason
混入上等社团聚会的真正原因
why you sneak into fancy faculty parties.
而不是因为你厌倦了叫拉面外卖
Not because you're sick of your ramen
打电动游戏什么的
and video games routine.
此时此刻  你的大脑飞速旋转着
And now, your mind is racing.
你在思索着要说点什么或是做点什么
You're wondering what you can possibly say or do
才能让我继续说话
to keep me on the line,
因为你极其不想
because the last thing you want
今晚剩下的时光跟这杯威士忌
is to spend the rest of the evening with that scotch
或你那乱蓬蓬头发的朋友一起度过
and that shaggy-haired friend of yours.
你知道问题出在哪吗
You know what your problem is?
你很帅气
You're pretty.
瞎了也是如此有格调
You even work the blind thing.
但你很蠢
But you're dumb.
你开始行动前就已经输了
You lost before you even stepped to the plate.
从一双老式皮鞋你就能得出这么多结论吗
You get all of that from a pair of old wingtips?
学得挺快
Quick study.
-你想知道我怎么想的吗  -说吧
- You wanna know what I think? - Tell me.
我觉得游戏才刚开始
I think the game's just beginning.
因为尽管你对龙舌兰酒很挑剔
Because despite your artisan tequilas
和礼仪课学来的的行为举止
and charm-school manners...
尽管比上帝还有钱
Despite being richer than God
让全世界萦绕在你指尖
and having the whole world at your fingertips...
你也很无聊
you're just bored.
是吗
Really?
无聊到花费时间研究一个陌生人的鞋子
Bored enough to spend your time studying a stranger's shoes.
我觉得你快烦死这个死板的聚会了
See, I think you were dying on the vine of this tight-ass party,
因为老爸的钱买不到你想要的那件东西
because Daddy's money can't buy you the one thing you really need.
什么东西
And what's that?
意外之物
The unexpected.
也许你没那么傻
Maybe you're not so dumb.
艾丽卡·纳齐丝
Elektra Natchios.
马特·默多克
Matt Murdock.
我们走  马修
Let's go, Matthew.
你左边
On your left.
喜欢吗
Do you like it?
听起来很昂贵
Sounds expensive.
听力不错
You have good ears.
-是你的吗  -对
- Is it yours? - It is.
到我们被警察逮住之前
Until we get caught.
陶瓦先生
Mr. Tower?
你要是能提前打个电话  我能准备一下
Uh, I wish you'd called. I'd have set something up.
-他们都在吗  -就尼尔森在
- Are they in? - Uh, just the Nelson half.
怎么了
What's the problem?
我们要谈谈
We need to talk.
单独谈谈
In private.
惹毛她真的不是个好主意
You know, it's really not a good idea to piss her off.
有什么可以为助理地方检察官效劳的
So, what can I do for the Assistant District Attorney?
说为你效劳更贴切  尼尔森先生
It's more what I can do for you, Mr. Nelson.
我们需要你手上关于格罗托的全部文件
We need all your files on the Grote case.
笔记  谈话  所有的录音和电子邮件
Notes, interviews, any and all recordings and e-mails.
作为回报  我们能得到
And in return, we get...
我说服雷耶斯地检
I convince District Attorney Reyes
把尼尔森和默多克的名字从黑名单上划掉
to scratch the names Nelson and Murdock off her shit-list.
真有那个名单吗
There's an actual list?
-尼尔森先生  我  -抱歉
- Mr. Nelson, I-- - I'm sorry.
相信我  这个惩罚者的烂摊子
Believe me, the sooner this Punisher mess
越快办妥越好
is off our plate, the better.
那  让我看看传票  然后
So... show me a subpoena, and...
有什么问题吗
Is there a problem?
你真打算让我为了这点事大动干戈吗
Are you really going to make me jump through hoops for this?
相信我  我只想老老实实地
Trust me, there's nothing I'd rather do more
配合你的公务
than cooperate with your office.
但要想一家律所分享跟客户的私密谈话
But a legal firm sharing privileged communications with a client,
即使客户已死  但没有法院指令
I mean, even a deceased one, without a court order?
我见过律师因为更小的事而被吊销执照
I've seen lawyers get disbarred for less.
我不清楚你什么情况
And I don't know about you,
但我为了拿到法律学位费尽了千辛万苦
but I worked really hard for my law degree.
挑灯熬夜
Nights and everything.
雷耶斯
Reyes...
她把她所有的政治筹码
she staked all her political chips
都压到了给这个惩罚者定罪上了
on the conviction of this Punisher freak.
如果事情随她愿
Now, if things'll go her way,
在不久的将来  地检办公室
there'll be an opening in the District Attorney's office
就会有个空职
in the not-so-distant future.
而陶瓦助理地检有志于此
And DA Tower has a nice ring to it.
换我肯定会开始考虑如果更配合
Now, I'd start considering the benefits that could accrue
能带来什么好处
if your firm were more... cooperative.
我都说了
Like I said...
拿出传票  我会跟孙子一样配合你
show me a subpoena, and I'll cooperate like a son of a bitch.
雷耶斯会像坦克一样碾压你们的
Reyes is gonna roll over you like a tank.
你总是这么说
You keep saying that.
然而
And yet...
我不还在这儿吗
still kinda here.
夜迦富大楼
我要赔钱的
I'm gonna have to pay for that.
我帮你出了
I'll stake you.
这就是大名鼎鼎的福格威尔健身房啊
So this is the famous Fogwell's.
对  赶紧吸几口气
Yeah, breathe it in fast.
如果我们因为非法入侵被捕了
If we get arrested for breaking and entering,
可就不好玩了
the fun kinda stops.
看来你知道被捕的滋味
Shows what you know.
我有段时间没来这儿了
I haven't been here in a while.
我打赌一切都没变
I bet nothing's moved.
-多谢  -你告诉我
- Thanks. - So tell me.
一个盲人怎么打拳击
How does a blind man box?
我不打  我不会打
I don't... I can't.
我爸  他曾是拳击手
My dad, he was the boxer.
曾
Was?
对  他死了
Yeah, he died.
抱歉
I'm sorry.
我只是过来  感受汗液的气味
I just come here to... breathe in the smell of sweat.
听听栓沙袋的铁链的声音
Hear the clank of the chains holding the bags.
怀念他
Remember him.
你从没见过你父亲搏斗
You never saw your father fight.
我看他被暴揍  数都数不清了
Oh, I saw him get his ass beat more times than I can count.
我不是天生就瞎
I wasn't born blind.
那就得另说了
That's a... whole other story.
他是在场上死的吗
Did he die in the ring?
不是  拳击没有害死他
No, boxing didn't kill him.
那是什么
What did?
集团犯罪
Organized crime.
像黑帮杀人那样吗
Like a mob hit?
-他是个罪犯吗  -不是
- Was he a criminal? - No.
但我觉得你可以说他不应该惹毛一些人
But I guess you could say he rubbed some people the wrong way.
有具体的名字吗
Someone in particular?
有
Uh, yeah.
一个叫罗斯科·斯威尼的人
A guy named Roscoe Sweeney.
我不知道是不是他开的枪  但是他下的令
I don't know if he pulled the trigger, but he gave the order.
你试过找到那个人渣吗
Did you ever try to find that piece of shit?
试过一次  那时我还小
Yeah, once. When I was a kid.
一无所获  只能忍了
Got nothing. Learned to live with it.
他可能躲起来了
He probably went underground.
我希望是躲到坟墓里了
Well, six feet, I hope.
你不必为我感到难过
You don't have to feel sorry for me.
我没有
I don't.
你确定吗
Are you sure?
当然
Yes.
我都看出来了
I've seen it.
过去几个礼拜  时不时的
Here and there, over the past few weeks.
你的内在可比你的外表深刻多了
You're so much more than you let on.
是吗
Okay.
我倒觉得这十分钟我告诉你的
I feel like I've told you more in the last ten minutes
比我过去十年告诉任何人的都多
than I've told anyone else in ten years.
我就知道
I knew it.
知道什么
You knew what?
你说你看不见
You said you were blind.
不  是你说我看不见的
No, you said I was blind.
这么说你能看见
So you can see?
一言难尽
It's complicated.
那你呢  你说你学的是芭蕾
What about you? You said you took ballet lessons.
我是学了
I did.
那是冬天
In the winters,
教我巴西战舞的老师回安哥拉的时候学的
when my capoeira master returned to Angola.
这是泰拳
Muay Thai?
-半个月一练  -是吗
- Every other Thursday. - Of course.
你打到我了
You got me.
那就快反击
Get me back.
反击
Get me!
我赢了
I win.
也就赢了这一轮
Yeah, first round, maybe.
这才刚刚开始呢
We're just getting started.
纳齐丝小姐  下午好
Ms. Natchios, good afternoon.
下午好  各位请坐
Good afternoon. You can sit.
我们希望您知道我们罗克森公司
We hope you know how valuable your business is
非常重视与您的业务合作
to the Roxxon Corporation.
谢谢
Thank you.
这位是斯坦·吉布森
This is Stan Gibson.
是我公司日本分支的财务专员
He's the money man for our Japanese arm.
所以他可以回答您的问题
So, he'll have the answers you're looking for.
至于他能不能用您听得懂的话回答清楚
Whether or not he can put them in terms you'll understand
就得另说了
is another matter.
那我们就赶快开始吧
Let's all prepare to be dazzled, shall we?
-打扰了  埃里森先生  -什么事
- Excuse me, uh, Mr. Ellison? - Yeah?
抱歉打扰了  我是凯伦·佩吉
Sorry, I don't mean to interrupt. My name is Karen Page.
-我认识...  -本
- I was a friend of-- - Ben.
我记得你
Yeah, I remember.
我觉得我该向您道歉
Look, I think that I owe you an apology.
-在葬礼上我以为你...  -算了
- At the funeral, I thought that you-- - Forget it.
本...
Look, Ben...
他实在是让我头大
Ben was a real pain in my ass.
所以我估计着他的朋友也好不哪去
So it follows that his friends would be, too.
你有什么事吗
What can I do for you?
我想你不会喜欢我的回答
Well, I don't think you're gonna like my answer.
我想和你谈谈弗兰克·卡塞尔的报道
I'd like to talk to you about the Frank Castle article.
-我知道  太吓人了  -也太不准确了
- I know, terrifying. - Also inaccurate.
听着
Look...
那篇报道我们是经过多方查实的
that article was corroborated by multiple sources.
纽约警方  地检  甚至还有几个目击证人
NYPD, DA's office, we even had some eyewitnesses.
没错  你们报道的事都没错
Yes, everything that you reported is correct.
让我放不下的是你们没报道的事
It's what you haven't reported that bothers me.
你们忽略了一些事实  所以不准确
The article is inaccurate by omission.
这边来  过来
Okay, come here, come here.
抱歉  请回避一下
Excuse me, please.
那边去
Go.
你是否知道在两年前
Right, did you know that two years ago,
弗兰克·卡塞尔上尉因为在阿富汗表现优异
Lieutenant Frank Castle was awarded the Navy Cross
赢得了海军十字勋章吗
for his service in Afghanistan, right?
级别仅次于荣誉勋章
That's second only to the Medal of Honor.
这个人是个战争英雄
This guy is a war hero.
只要一有大规模枪击案要报道
Military history is the first thing we search
我们首先要查的就是参军史
whenever there's a mass shooting.
所以我们知道他曾经参加海军陆战队
So, we know that he was a Marine recruit,
而且还知道他入役时非常年轻
and we know that he went in as a kid,
但没有发现他真正服过役的证据
but there's no evidence that he actually served.
我亲眼见过他的勋章
I've seen the medal,
卡塞尔的名字就镌刻在上面
engraved with Castle's name,
旁边就是他和国防部长握手的照片
next to a photograph of him shaking the secretary's hand.
你是说他的服役史是机密吗
Are you suggesting that his work was classified?
我不知道  但我觉得是这样
I don't know, but-- but I would assume.
别觉得  你在哪看见的
Don't assume. Where'd you see it?
这不重要吧
Uh, not important.
相当重要
Pretty important.
你的报道还说他没有已知的亲属
Look, your article also states that he had no known relatives,
而且纽约的每家报纸都这么说
but every paper in New York says that.
因为地检发的新闻简报里是这么说的
Well, that was in the press briefing issued by the DA's office.
他有家人
He had a family.
有过一个妻子  玛丽亚·伊丽莎白
He had a wife, Maria Elizabeth,
还有过一个女儿  丽莎·芭芭拉
a daughter, Lisa Barbara,
还有过一个儿子  小弗兰克
and a son, Frank Junior.
-有过  -他们都去世了
- Had? - All dead.
死亡时间和卡塞尔头部中枪
Killed around the same time that Castle was hospitalized
被送医的时间差不多
for a gunshot wound to the head.
怎么  难道说
What, so...
难道你是在说
What, you're saying that
他杀死了自己的家人然后朝自己开枪
he murdered his family and then shot himself?
某种创伤后应激障碍造成的杀人事件
Some sort of PTSD murder-suicide attempt?
不  如果真的是这样的话
No, see, if that's what had happened,
地检肯定会在简报里提到
the DA would have put it in her brief,
兴许会大号加粗标出来
in flashing neon if she could,
因为这能佐证她认为他精神不正常的说法
because that supports her story that he's a psychopath.
那你以为真相是什么
So, what do you think really happened?
这我目前还不清楚
That's what I don't know yet.
不过如果我能查一查你们的资料库
But if I could dig through your files
或者翻翻你们的过刊
or I could check into your back issues,
也许能有所发现
maybe I could figure it out.
而我的任何发现  证实的任何故事
And anything that I find, anything that I can prove--
独家报道权全归《公报》
The Bulletin gets the exclusive.
成交
Deal.
那好  成交
Okay, deal.
你先别高兴得太早
don't do any somersaults yet.
所有的...
All the, uh...
所有的服务器都在事故中被清空净了
All the servers were completely wiped in the incident.
几十年的记录全都  没了
Decades, just... gone.
所以我们现在只用纸质版保存了
So, um, we keep hard copies of everything now.
我的天  有什么存放顺序吗
Jeez! Are they in any kind of order?
大概有吧
Um, you know, roughly.
我看你最好从这里找起
I would... I would start, uh, down here.
好的  多谢
Okay. Uh, thanks.
怎么了
What?
没什么  我只是在想  如果
Uh, nothing, I'm just thinking, uh, somewhere...
本·尤里克在天上看着这一切的话
Ben Urich is looking down, and just...
肯定会很高兴的
getting a real kick out of all this.
搜索愉快
Have fun.
我知道你们肯定还有私事要忙
I'm sure you all have places to be, things to do.
要去见老婆  见情人
With your wives, your mistresses...
但我有几个问题
But I have questions.
而这个子公司具体是做什么的
And this subsidiary, what is it exactly?
-是一家医药公司  -主营业务是
- A medical company. - And they do?
-医药研发  -真是具体啊
- Studies. - How specific.
主要研究止痛药  特效药之类
Research for pain relievers, treatments for diseases.
具体药品名字我不能透露
The names of which I mostly can't pronounce.
并购决策是怎么做出来的
How do you determine your acquisitions?
这个...
Well--
请见谅
Excuse me.
我们的服务器出了点问题
There's an issue with our server.
Someone has hacked into the server.
有人黑进了我们的服务器
Possibly internal, we don't know yet,
security is looking into it.
可能来自内部  还不清楚  保安正在查
If it's an external threat,
I'm sure they can trace the IP address
如果是外部威胁  我想他们会追查到IP地址
and deal with the "problem" face-to-face.
然后会当场"解决问题"
But I'm more concerned
about what information
不过我最担心的是服务器下线时
they can pull from Roxxon's system
when it is offline.
他们会从罗克森的服务器上偷取什么信息
实在是非常抱歉  出了一点事
I'm terribly sorry, something has come up.
我们能改天再行商议吗
Could we reconvene at another time?
当然
Absolutely.
谢谢
Thank you.
我会找人护送您下楼的
I'll have someone escort you downstairs.
谢谢
Thank you.
在这座城市  一个女孩子家非常需要帮助
In this city, a girl needs all the help she can get.
怎么是灰色的
Why is it gray?
生活就是这么神秘
One of life's mysteries.
他们橄榄用光了
They were out of olives.
那么
So?
So...
什么
What?
我今天过的不顺
It was a hard day.
我就想和你聚一聚  喝一杯什么的
I thought we could catch up, you know, have a drink.
就是
Just...
像以前一样
be like we were.
普普通通地
Normal.
我几个月没听见你一点消息
I haven't heard from you in months.
这个
Well, that's...
也没那么不正常  对吧
not all that abnormal, right?
也许你说得对
Yeah, I guess you're right.
那咱们大喝一场  互相吐苦水吧
Let's get trashed and tell each other our sob stories.
你先请
You first.
马特在和我们的办公室助理约会
Matt's dating our office assistant.
就是那个又好看  又合你口味的金发妞
The cute one? Blonde, totally your type?
没错
Yeah.
正确的答案是
The correct answer is,
"你才是我的真命天女  玛茜"
"No one is as perfect for me as you, Marci."
还不止这一件
Gets worse.
过去一个小时内我们失去了两个客户
We lost two clients in the last hour.
就像我之前丢了在兰德曼-扎克的工作似的
Oh, it's kinda like when I lost the job at Landman and Zack.
-还好有别家律所在招聘  -我是说真的
- Thank God HC and B was hiring. - No, I'm serious.
就是地检
It's the DA.
我在她起诉惩罚者的案子上让她下不来台
I called her bluff on a case she's building against the Punisher
结果她反倒来劲了
and she doubled down.
她盯上我们了
She's coming after us.
这样啊
I see.
你这次叫我不是叙旧的
You didn't call me for a social drink.
你是叫我来帮忙的
You called me for help.
这样才叫正常
That feels more normal.
好吧
Fine.
我的新合伙人中间有传闻说
Rumors among my new partners,
雷耶斯志在市长大位
Reyes has her sights on the mayor's office.
我真是"吃了一惊"
This is my shocked face.
而她上位的手段就是
And she aims to do so by...
拿给弗兰克·卡塞尔定罪做跳板
building a platform on Frank Castle's conviction.
她拿下他
She gets him...
她就能依此判例拿下以后所有的义警了
she sets precedent against these other vigilantes popping up.
我们律所有一位已经在接受审查了
One in our office is already under serious scrutiny,
是一个叫杰西卡·琼斯的小姑娘
lady by the name of Jessica Jones.
你知道我觉得下一个是谁吗
Oh, and you know who I bet is next?
有角的那个
The horny one.
就是  夜魔侠
It's... Daredevil.
你觉得会成功吗
You think it'll work?
她打算利用这些城市灾难为自己谋福
She's gonna turn city-wide disaster into damn fine lemonade.
这是她的宏图大业
It's her big power play.
肯定会管用的
It's gonna work.
都已经  三个小时了
It's been... whoa, three hours.
天啊
Oh, God.
我快来不及去吃晚餐了
And I'm almost late for dinner.
-多谢  -有发现吗
- Thanks. - Any luck?
卡塞尔中枪的那一周
Well, these are all the papers
所有的报纸都在这了
from the week that Castle was shot.
我已经反复看了三遍了
I've been through each one of them three times,
一个字都没提到卡塞尔和他的家人
and there's not a single mention of Castle, his family...
连符合他特征的无名氏都没有
Not even a John Doe that matches.
什么都没有
Just nothing.
你也知道  每天都有人中枪
Well, you know, people are shot every day.
不是每一枪都能打上报纸
It doesn't always make the paper.
你看到什么就是什么
Cleavered Cleavers.
什么意思
What's that?
就是我们报纸圈的一条老格言
Ah, just an old newspaper adage, right?
如果有人全家横遭不幸  那就是全国大新闻
If horror befalls a family you can paint as all-American,
肯定会上头条
it makes the front page.
所以如果卡塞尔一家没上报
So, if the Castles are not in this paper,
那就说明有人不想让这事登报
it's because somebody wants to keep it quiet.
见鬼
Well, shit.
4月14日
April 14th.
卡塞尔一家遇害是什么时候
When was the Castle family murdered?
我估计肯定是那一周前后吧
Well, I figure it's gotta be sometime that week, right?
跟你说  我记不住自己孩子的生日  但是
You know, I cannot remember my... my kids' birthdays, but...
极其血腥暴力的血案我却记得清清楚楚
violent, soul-sucking events are just seared into my brain.
也难怪
Figures, right?
在这里
Ah, yes, yes.
帮派火并
Okay, gang-on-gang violence.
因为没有平民伤亡的报道  所以也没人在乎
No civilians were reported injured, so nobody cared.
我花了一周才把这条新闻登出去
It took me a week to get this in the paper.
你看
Here.
三个帮派  在中央公园  正午
Three gangs, Central Park, mid-day.
互相开枪打成一团  简直就是屠杀
They shot each other to shit. It was a total massacre.
中央公园大战
墨西哥黑帮  地狱狂犬
Mexican Cartel, Dogs of Hell...
-厨房爱尔兰帮  -厨房爱尔兰帮
- Kitchen Irish. - Kitchen Irish.
-就是这三家  -被惩罚者屠了
- Those were all the three-- - That the Punisher gunned down.
-这其中肯定有联系  -是
- There's gotta be a connection, right? - Mmm-hmm. Right.
-我的天  -什么
- Oh, my God. - What?
我的天啊
Oh, my God.
当地黑帮与纽约警方
激烈枪战
就是这里
This is it.
他的家人就是在这被杀的
This is where his family was killed.
现在该怎么办
Shit, what do I do now?
核实
Confirm it.
-能暂借给我吗  -当然
- Can I borrow this? - Yeah, sure.
不过我得提醒你
Just a little reminder...
《公报》可是有独家报道权啊
Bulletin gets the exclusive, right?
-当然  老大  -你现在就走
- You got it, boss. - Wait, you're going now?
不是吧
Really?
你喝葡萄酒吗
Do you drink wine?
我应该先问清楚的
I should know that.
乔茜酒吧不卖的我都不喝
I don't drink anything they don't serve at Josie's.
我倒是没看见菜单上有什么便宜酒水
Yeah, well, I don't see swill on the menu.
-你今天...  -今天你...
- So how was-- - So what did--
-抱歉我...  -我刚刚是...
- I'm sorry-- - I was just gonna--
你来  你先说吧
Uh, you go ahead. Go, go first.
你今天过得如何
How was your day?
还行
Fine.
就是普通的工作日
Uh, yeah, just a regular day at the office.
这比之前要好多了吧
Well, it's a nice change of pace, right?
没人朝你开枪了
Not being shot at?
-肯定感觉很好  -是啊
- That's gotta feel good. - Yeah.
那你  你的新客户怎么样
You, how's the, uh, new client?
嗯
Uh, yeah, um...
也没什么新鲜的
Nothing I haven't seen before.
我觉得很有可能谈不成  不过
I seriously doubt it's gonna pan out, but that's...
也还好
That's fine.
那挺好的
Okay, good.
工作聊完了
Well, that covers work.
我们可以再聊别的
Uh, well, it's a start.
-我一会儿就回来  -好
- Um, I'll be back in just a minute, um... - Yeah.
-点些好的  -行
- Order something fantastic. - Sure.
-先生  -如果我想在一分钟内
- Sir? - Look. If I had to seem like
装出我了解一切能了解的
I knew everything there is to know about wines
有关葡萄酒的知识  我应该点什么酒
in the next 60 seconds, what would I... what would I order?
-您是马修·默多克吗  -是
- Matthew Murdock? - Yeah.
有您的电话
You have a call.
多谢
Oh, thanks.
我是默多克
This is Murdock.
抱歉打扰你幽会的雅兴
Sorry to bother you while you're out,
但是她回来之前你有空说几句话吧
but you have a few moments before she returns, right?
你又想要我怎样
What do you want from me?
这个问题该问你自己
You should ask yourself the same question.
楼顶上那一出真是可爱
That rooftop act was cute.
和你少女有难的戏码比起来差得远
Yeah, nothing compared to your damsel-in-distress one.
你说得对  我其实不需要你
Oh, you're right. I didn't actually need you.
我说了  也许我只是想你了
I told you, maybe I just missed you.
不过别担心  钱你留着吧
But don't worry, you can keep the money.
去死吧你
Go to hell.
如果你真的再也不想跟我打交道
If you really want to be done,
就当这通电话是我解雇你吧
consider this me firing you.
想开就随时拿去开
Any time you want to drive...
我觉得失明人士开车是非法的吧
I think it's illegal, driving under the influence of blindness.
你可是前途无量的大律师
You're the future lawyer.
那我该返校重修了
Yeah, I should start going to class again, then.
-我们这是在哪  -房子
- Hey, where are we? - A house.
是你家的房子吗
Yeah. Is it yours?
当然不是  我在郊区可住不下去
Oh, God, no. I'd die in the suburbs.
这座可爱的小公馆
No, this charming little chateau
是我爸一个合作伙伴的房子
belongs to one of my father's many work associates,
现在他人去蒙特卡洛合法嫖娼去了
who's currently off to Monte Carlo, where prostitution is legal.
那么
So...
你有钥匙吧
you have the keys, right?
欢迎回家  亲爱的  晚饭快好了
Welcome home, darling. Dinner's almost ready.
好小的厨房
Tiny kitchen.
这里有
Okay, so we have, uh...
松露  红肠  腌黄瓜
truffles, saucissons, cornichons...
-就是小黄瓜  -不吃
- Baby pickles. - No.
好吧  不吃小黄瓜
Okay, got it. No cornichons.
那么
So...
等你毕了业
when you graduate...
我们结了婚
and we get married...
然后买栋房子  不止一栋  抱歉
...and we buy a house... I mean, houses, sorry.
要在圣托里尼岛  圣塞瓦斯蒂安
Santorini, San Sebastian...
还有巴黎  等我们想住城里就回来住
Paris, for when we're feeling cosmopolitan.
这
This...
就是我们的生活方式
is how we'll live.
那孩子们呢
And what about the kids?
怎么安排孩子们
What are we gonna do with them?
我们可爱的小艾莉
Oh, you know, sweet little Ellie, and...
还有她的傻弟弟  小马特
her simpleton brother, Matty Junior...
可以给我们做饭扫地
...can cook and clean
采购食品  好让我们有时间去...
and stock the fridge for us, so we can use...
做喜欢做的事
our time doing better things.
比如说做爱吗
Like sex?
就是做爱
Exactly like sex.
你渴吗
Who's thirsty?
-你觉得好不好  -什么
- Is it good? - What?
这个
This.
这一切  这...
All of this, this, uh...
这种生活
life.
非常好啊
It's fantastic.
但我愿意拿这一切换一辈子闻到你身上的气息
But I would trade it all in for a lifetime of smelling your skin.
干杯
Cheers.
-听起来很贵  -我猜也是
- Sounded expensive. - I'm guessing.
我才不管
I don't care.
懂我吗
Get me?
我明白你
I do, I get you.
你怎么这么笨
When are you going to learn?
抓我啊
Get me.
我学聪明了
I have learned.
你很了解我
You know me.
没人像你这么了解我  而我也很了解你
Like no one else ever has. And I know you.
我们属于彼此
We belong together.
有人来了
Someone's here.
老爸朋友的伟哥可能用光了
Daddy's friend probably ran out of Viagra--
有脚步声  走得很快  我去看看
They're footsteps. Moving fast. Let me go check.
不不不  你待在这里
No, no, no, no, no. You stay here.
如果我去跟他解释  他不会生气的
If I explain everything, he won't be mad.
我保证
I promise.
马修  还记得罗斯科·斯威尼
Matthew, you remember Roscoe Sweeney,
那个杀了你父亲的混蛋吗
the son of a bitch who killed your father?
没事吧
Everything okay?
-没事  他们的红酒卖光了  -不是吧
- Yeah, they ran out of wine. - No.
等等  你说真的
Wait, seriously?
马特
Matt...
我不...喜欢这个地方
I don't... I don't like this place, you know?
你是不喜欢这里还是...
Is it the place? Or is it--
绝对不是因为你
It's definitely not you.
-你肯定吗  -非常肯定
- You're sure? - Yeah. I'm positive.
来  我知道我们可以去哪
Come on. I know where we can go.
-谢谢  -闻起来好香
- Thank you. - Wow, this smells amazing.
是什么
What is it?
管它是什么呢  反正有酒
Who cares? They have wine.
那倒是
Right.
好吧
That's...
廉价的东西总是让我
You know, I've always felt more comfortable
喝得更自在
with the cheap stuff.
-知道吗  -是吗
- You know? - Yeah?
来  敬你这句话
Well, here, I'll drink to that.
廉价的东西
Cheap stuff.
直到几个月前  我才开始吃印度菜
You know, I never even had Indian food until a few months ago.
怎么会
How is that possible?
我在佛蒙特州的老家大约只有四百个人
Well, my hometown in Vermont had about 400 people,
最有异国风味的菜就是薯条
so the most ethnic food it offered was French fries.
所以你来纽约
So that's why you, uh, came to New York?
就为了这些吃的吗
For the... for the food?
当然不是
Uh, no.
但如果我知道这家店的存在
Although, if I knew places like this existed,
我老早就离开佛蒙特州了
I'd have left Vermont ages ago.
这就是我喜欢这座城市的原因
You see, that's why I love this city.
我一辈子都住在这里
I've lived here my whole life, and...
这儿到处都有新的秘密
the place never stops unfolding new secrets.
知道吗
Yeah, you know...
虽然纽约时不时
despite the crime, and the darkness,
会出现罪行和黑暗  但却让我觉得
every once in a while, New York makes me feel...
很安全吗
Like, safe?
-是的  很奇怪吧  -这个嘛
- Yes, is that weird? - Well...
我明白
I get it.
希望你能看看这家店
I wish you could see this place.
如果你描述给我听  我就能看到
I can, if you describe it to me.
不管怎样  我最喜欢的
So, anyways, my favorite part...
就是天花板
is the ceiling.
真的就是布满了无数的灯泡
So, it's literally dripping with thousands of lights.
它们的形状就像是辣椒
They're shaped like chili peppers...
我知道听来真的有点俗气  但不是那样的
which sounds really tacky, I know, but it's, um, it's not.
只是
Just...
富有魔力
It's magic.
我到了
This is me.
你真的不是
Are you sure you don't...
住在更远的地方吗
live two more blocks?
-或许再远一点  -我也想
- Maybe three? - I wish.
我们可以坐下来
We could sit.
好
Yeah.
我要亲你了
All right, I'm gonna kiss ya.
你可以上楼
You could come up...
如果你想的话
if you like.
我很想
I would love to.
但是你不会
But you won't.
今晚不行
Not tonight.
-没事  -我能
- It's okay. - Can I...
我能告诉你原因吗
Can I tell you why?
因为我有这种
Because I have this...
不可思议的能力
incredible ability to bring...
会给我人生中最美好的事物带去灾难
disaster to the best things in my life
而今晚很完美
and tonight has been perfect.
你不觉得吗
Don't you think?
是的
Yes.
如果现在结束  我就能保留这个完美的夜晚
And if I stop now, then I get to keep this one perfect night.
同时有机会让明天也这么完美
And also have the chance of keeping it going tomorrow.
后天
And the day after...
大后天
And the day after that...
都能保持下去
And the...
没错
Exactly.
看来该说晚安了
Then I guess it's good night...
默多克先生
Mr. Murdock.
晚安  佩吉小姐
Good night, Ms. Page.
给点货  伙计  给点货
Fix me up, man? Fix me up.
我知道你是谁  我知道你是谁
I know who you are, man! I know who you are!
你有多少钱  你有多少钱
How much you got, man? How much you got?
老天爷
Oh, Jesus Christ.
等我逃出去
When I get out of this...
我会记住你们的脸
Oh, I'll remember your faces.
完完全全地记住
Every single bit of them...
我会追杀你们
I will hunt you!
你什么时候能挣脱呢
When you get out?
你在哪找到他的
Where did you find him?
在蒙特卡洛  我没骗你
Monte Carlo. I wasn't lying.
多年来他一直用的是化名
He's been going by an alias for years now.
艾尔·马里诺
Al Marino.
丑陋之人配丑恶之名
An ugly name for an ugly man.
你死定了
Oh, you're dead.
你们俩死定了
Both of ya!
玩过家家的孩子们
Couple of kids playing house!
管好你的嘴
Watch your tongue.
趁它还在的时候
While it's still attached.
他躲了起来  藏得很隐秘
He tried to hide. Went underground.
但是人渣总是会出现的
But the scum always rises.
艾尔就是藏不住
Al just couldn't stay anonymous.
他得花花他的黑心钱
He had to spend his blood money.
引人注目
Make a splash.
做个大人物
Be the big man.
这倒令我省了不少力
You made it easy for me.
吃屎吧你
Eat shit.
还想挨打吗
Want me to hit you again?
我还就不打了
Well, I won't.
他来打你
But he will.
我根本不认识他  但我一眼就能看出来
I don't know him from Christ, but one look and I can tell.
绣花枕头一个
Pretty boy ain't got it in him.
你不记得我了吗
You don't remember me?
你杀了我父亲
You killed my father.
真抱歉让你失望了  小子
Well, I hate to break it to you, son...
但是我杀了不少人的爹
but I killed a lot of guys' dads.
那让我提醒提醒你
Then let me help you.
他拳劲很大
He hit hard.
就像这样
Like this.
这也算拳劲大
You call that hard?
尽情打
Let it out.
使劲打
释放你心中的怒火
Okay? Whatever's inside you.
这是为了你父亲  马修
Do it for your father, Matthew.
为了我们
Do it for us.
来吧
Come on.
"马修"
"Matthew"?
你是拳手杰克的儿子
You're Battlin' Jack's boy!
你这小崽子
Oh, you amateur.
我算想起来你是谁了
Now I know your name.
我一定会拿你的血洗大街
Nothing'll stop me from bloodying the street with your corpse.
就像我当年办了你爹
Just like I did to your old man!
好
Yes.
了结吧
End it.
现在了结他
End it now.
-什么  -继续动手啊
- What? - Keep going.
不了...
No, that's, uh...
-我已经打够了  -不
- No, that's all I got. - No...
他知道了你的名字
He knows your name.
割了他的喉咙
Cut his throat.
宰了他
Kill him.
什么
What?
杀了他
Kill him.
我不能杀他
I can't do that.
你我一起  没什么不能的
We can do anything together.
记得吗
Remember?
不  我不能
No, I can't.
我还以为你理解我
I thought you understood me.
我也这么以为
Yeah, I thought I did, too.
我们需要报警
We need to call the police.
911  您有什么警情
911, what is your emergency?
我想举报一名通缉犯
Yes, I'd like to report the location of a wanted felon.
名字叫罗斯科·斯威尼
The name is Roscoe Sweeney.
请说地址
What is the address?
瞧  我就说你也想我
See? You missed me, too.
晚餐吃得开心吗
Did you have a nice dinner?
艾丽卡  我来是要问你一个问题
Elektra, I came here to ask you a question,
我希望你能回答我
and I'd like for you to answer it.
当初你为什么要带我去那间别墅
Why did you take me to that mansion?
你就想问这个
That's your question?
好玩呗
For fun.
好玩
For fun?
你觉得那好玩吗
That's fun for you?
逼着我去杀人
To try to push me into killing a man?
我没逼你做任何事
I didn't push you into anything.
你也没杀人
And you didn't kill anyone.
-但你想杀他  -不  我不想
- But you wanted to. - No, I didn't.
别  别这么说  现在别来这个
Don't do that, don't... Not now, don't...
你不要装得好像能看穿我的灵魂似的
You act like you have some window into my soul,
你从没看穿过  永远也不会
but you don't, and you never have.
你内心总是有那么一股凶猛的暗潮
There was always this glorious darkness inside you.
不
No.
所以我才带你去罗斯科·斯威尼家
That's why I took you to Roscoe Sweeney's.
而且是的
And, yes.
所以我才爱你
That's why I loved you.
所以你才爱我
That's why you loved me, too.
不要否认我们之间的火花
Don't deny what we have.
求你了
Please.
你以为那就是爱吗
You think that's what love is?
有人  有人来了
Someone... someone's coming.
电梯在移动
The elevator's moving--
还有
There's...
大厅里有消音手枪开枪了
There's a silencer in the lobby.
是谁  艾丽卡
Who is it, Elektra?
要我猜的话  就是日本黑帮
If I had to guess, Yakuza.
不  那不可能
No. No, that's impossible.
我消灭了日本黑帮
I took care of the Yakuza.
显然你没有  帮忙拿下手套
Clearly, you didn't. Hold my gloves?
今天在夜迦富大厦  我侵入了浅野公司
Today, at the Yakatomi Building, I infiltrated Asano,
罗克森的日本分支
the Japanese branch of Roxxon,
植入了一个小病毒弄垮了他们的系统
and I planted a little bug to crash their system.
我听到了
Yeah, I heard it.
你知道他们会来找你
You knew they'd come for you?
我知道他们会来这里
Well, I knew they'd come here.
这栋楼不在我名下  我又不是新手
This building isn't in my name. I'm no amateur.
等等  你知道我也会来吗
Hold on a second, did you know I'd come?
我挺有自信的
My confidence was high.
这是你设计好的
You planned this.
你在公寓说的每句话都是假的
Everything you said in the apartment, it's just lies.
你根本不是真心  你也没有歉意
You don't mean it, you're not sorry...
只是想操纵我
It's just manipulation with you.
-你一直都没变  -不是
- It's the same thing-- - No!
一次又一次  你只会操纵我
Over and over again, you just manipulate!
马修
Matthew!
-我说了  我了解你  -你不了解我
- I told you, I know you. - You don't.
我一直都了解你
I've always known you.
-过去了解  现在也了解  -你不了解我
- Then, and now. - No, you don't know me.
那你证明给我看啊
So, now, you tell me.
你自己能对付他们
You can handle them yourself.
这次也要我逼你吗
Do I need to push you this time?